# Beatrice Olofsson



"Beatrice is very competent and has broad knowledge of online and digital media. She is innovative, quick and responsible. I can warmly recommend her."

- Jenny Gustafsson,

Project Leader Go'kväll SVT

# **Contact**

T. +46 76 832 04 01

M. beatriceolofs@gmail.com linkedin.com/beatriceolofs

# **Profile**

I am a creative woman and experienced in designing a variety of digital content. I graduated with a bachelor's degree in Digital Media production and I have plenty of experience after my one year working for SVT. I am looking for a position where I can apply my knowledge and that allows me to grow as a creator.

# **Experience**

#### PRODUCER & EDITOR

SVT / STORYN BAKOM 5 2022

 Producer of childrens program Storyn Bakom, responsible for animation, editing and sound.

#### **PRODUCER & EDITOR**

SVT / SEXY HANDS ∫ 2022

· Producer and editor of content for social media and DUO-app.

### **ONLINE EDITOR & COMMUNITY MANAGER**

SVT ∫ 2022

- Identify, edit and publish content for SVTs social media and web, mainly Go'kväll and SVT Recept.

#### **VICE INFORMATION COMMITTEE**

UMEÅS MEDIE- & SYSTEMVETARFÖRENING ∫ 2019 - 2020

- Creator of digital content, responsible for social media and website design.

#### ARTIST

2013 - ONGOING

- Freelance artist of digital art.

# **Education**

#### DIGITAL MEDIA PRODUCTION

UMEÅ UNIVERSITET [ 2018 - 2021

#### ART PROGRAM

MIDGÅRDSSKOLAN [ 2014 - 2017

# **Oualities**

- Adobe Suite
- HTML (Bootstrap) & CSS
- Unity

- Asperite
- Maya
- CMS (Escenic)

# Nominiees

#### PRIX EUROPA 2022

2022 DIGITAL MEDIA PROJECTS

- Sexy Hands - Dating School

# PRIX ITALIA 2022

2022 WEB INTERACTIVE MEDIA

- Sexy Hands - Dating School

\* If interested, reference is provided.